♪ Once upon a time in the olden days ♪
♪ A sweet girl lived in the Bosphorus ♪
Dad!
My love.
Look.
Look what my father got for me.
What is this?
It's a mandolin.
Go on!
Where are we going?
Why are we leaving, mom?
We're going to a place
where no one can deceive us.
You'll have new friends.
We'll have a new house.
From now on,
we'll write our own destiny.
But I don't know how to write.
In that case, you'll sing.
Come on.
Don't keep the breath only in your head.
Send it down and let it
fill your ribs, Belgin.
One last time.
Don't lose heart, Belgin.
You are not only the voice.
you are also the instrument.
You should become the song itself.
I wish my father heard this too.
That I would be a song one day.
Belgin Sarilmiser.
What did you work on for us?
Erlkönig from Schubert, ma'am.
Oh! It's a difficult piece.
Why did you choose this one?
I was fascinated by its story, ma'am.
So what is the story about?
There is a father and his child.
The child is very sick.
The father takes the boy in his arm
and gets on horseback.
To rush him to the doctor.
And so they ride through a dark forest.
And what happens to the boy?
Unfortunately, his father can't save him.
Let us begin if you are ready.
Ms...
...it's nothing much but...
Oh, Ms Sabahat, you shouldn't have!
Oh, no, this is nothing
next to what you did for us.
You see she has siblings and all
but they're abroad.
Only Hatice is in Mersin.
What would we have done here
on our own without you?
Oh, come on, don't mention it.
If it hadn't been me,
it would have been someone else.
No, Ms, that's not the case.
No one can ignore such a voice.
No one can ignore Belgin.
Mom! Mom! I won!
I won!
Ms Suna, I won!
Look... And I won first place.
Oh, thank God...
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, Ms.
Well done, my girl.
Well, mom...
...it says on the list that
I'm to be a boarding student.
Ms, what is she talking about?
I won't allow such a thing.
We'll take care of the boarding matter.
- Well done.
- Thank you, Ms.
My girl, where are you?
Ms Suna is leaving.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What are you writing?
What is it you are hiding?
Are you writing to your father again?
I'm writing to tell him
I won the conservatory exam. What of it?
Has he ever asked you once
if you needed anything? No.
Anyway, so be it...
If you say so.
1 YEARS LATER
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, my girl.
Come on, your time is up.
Your time is up.
Let's invite Belgin too. Belgin...
...let's go to the canteen.
No, you go ahead. I need to wait
for the extra study session again.
You don't go out to eat with us anymore.
Aren't you hungry?
You're coming to my birthday, right?
My father made a reservation
at Feyman Club for us.
It won't be the same without you.
You have to come.
If nothing goes wrong.
Sort it out. Won't be the same
without you. Hope to see you there.
Please.
- Hope to see you there.
- See you.
- Can I take a look at this?
- Of course, there you go.
Thank you.
Hello, can I help you?
I'm looking for a cello.
The son of a fisherman from Bergen
made that cello.
He's a very important luthier right now.
Bergen.
I love it.
- How much is it?
- 16 thousand Liras.
Thank you.
I'll buy the cello.
Not today but I will.
Can you keep this for me?
Don't sell it to anyone.
Have a good day.
Mom.
Welcome.
Mom...
- I've got something to tell you.
- Hm?
But you are not to get angry.
I need to buy a cello immediately.
- Immediately, eh?
- Immediately.
I'm lagging behind in my studies.
I wait in line for hours.
If I have my own instrument,
I'll make a quicker progress.
Well, you need to bite
the bullet a little bit.
I already do.
I wear your old clothes.
I can't go down to the canteen
with anyone. What else can I do?
You see the state we're in.
Just bite the bullet a little bit.
We'll buy it next year.
Mom, a cello is 16 thousand Liras!
16 thousand!
We can't buy it even if you sew
wedding dresses for years.
Finish school, get a job and
buy one for yourself.
That's what I'm talking about.
I've decided to work.
I'll buy it myself.
You must have gone mad.
You have a single job to do
and that's to study.
The post office will employ officers.
- Oh, she's still talking about a job.
- And they pay quite well too.
I'll make five times more than
what you make.
Do you hear yourself?
- You're not even of age!
- We'll fake it.
Stop insisting!
No way!
You don't have my permission.
Listen, a bead worker named Havva would
visit our neighbourhood.
She would have the girls sit...
...and look at their palms first and then,
eye their face taking her time...
...she would pick beads from
her counter one by one and...
...string a destiny necklace.
And there was this blabber-mouthed Nilgun,
she came running one day.
I don't know where she found the money.
She said, "I want one too".
And Havva said okay.
She sat the girl across from her.
She looked at her palm and then, her face.
And then, she strung a simple, ordinary...
...necklace using wooden beads...
...and placed it on her neck.
Nilgun was very offended, of course.
"Why does mine look like this while
every else's look beautiful?" she asked.
"Because you are an impatient girl,"
she said.
"And this is the necklace
of impatient girls."
And what did your necklace look like?
I could never afford one.
Come on, get up...
Your sister sent dry eggplants.
I cooked stuffed eggplants.
Set the table.
You have a collect call from Tokat.
Do you take it?
I do.
I'm leaving.
Girl, Belgin.
You look like a doll.
I'll cover for you next week, I promise.
Belgin is here.
Come on, sing.
♪ I wish you remembered me
for one last time ♪
♪ Gave me that call one more time ♪
♪ I wish we could pour out our grief to
each other when we are lonely ♪
♪ We are both
in need of a friend after all ♪
♪ Why don't you think about
it for one last time? ♪
♪ If someone like me shows up ♪
♪ And begs for the love of the old days ♪
♪ Don't break her heart and turn her down ♪
♪ You were with me years ago ♪
♪ You couldn't see the future ♪
♪ Is it only I who made a mistake ♪
♪ If I'm not too late, forgive me, darling ♪
♪ If I'm not too late,
forgive me, darling. ♪
Where have you been?
It's late and I've been worried sick.
- Where were you?
- Are you still up?
I wish you had let me know!
And you went there in my client's dress.
Alright, mom, stop.
- Take them off... Take it off.
- Stop... Leave me alone.
Where were you fooling around
till this hour?
I'm so glad I went there!
If you had been there, you wouldn't have
been able to believe your eyes.
All the customers stopped
eating and drinking.
Even the waiters stopped to listen to me.
The waiter?! Where...
Where did you do?!
That moment, when I sang...
...something happened...
...all the lyrics...
...went right through me.
It was as if the entire world
had stopped...
...and only I existed.
Only my voice.
I became the song from head to toe.
It was so beautiful.
I was riveted to the ground.
Mom...
...I became famous within one minute
in the club.
The club?
Girl, what club?
Did you go to a club?
Mom,
don't you hear what I'm talking about?
I said I sang a song.
If I get on that stage,
I'll never come down again.
I'll tear your legs apart!
You ‘ve got school! So, study!
I can't believe this is what
you aspire to!
Aspiration?
It's love, love.
I won't sew underwear for people's bottoms
for pittance like you.
I will sing.
Here came your guy again.
He not only writes a letter
but also sticks a stamp on it.
He literally spends all his money
on stamps.
Thank you.
Let me take it.
I wrote it to you.
It's an invitation.
I don't like milk pudding.
No, it's not for the milk pudding place.
I don't go to amusement parks,
it's very boring.
I've never thought of it.
Is it for the movie theatre?
Mersin Idman Yurdu, we have a match
He invited me to a football match.
He's mad.
Shall we dance?
Why?
Because we're in a wedding.
If you don't know how to,
we can do the halay dance too.
Okay, if I don't, we will.
Are you shaking?
No, why should I?
It's cold.
How do you know these moves?
I've been dancing with my jacket
for a week.
It didn't work, it didn't work.
Alright, don't bring yourself down.
We'll start from the beginning.
I don't bring myself down, you do.
You can't tell me how it's done.
Look in the mirrors.
Do you see everything?
If you check the mirrors, you're safe.
The mirrors don't hide anything.
Put your foot on the clutch.
Disconnect the contact between
the gear and the engine.
So what is it?
You won't listen to your mind,
you'll listen to your heart.
Shift the gear to neutral.
This...
...is the first gear, okay?
And it's our commitment to each other.
What a nice way to tell me.
Clutch again.
It's our heart.
The second gear.
And this is our engagement.
Oh, we got to the engagement so quickly.
That's the nature of engagements.
We can't delay the engagement.
See, we're making way so nicely...
But...
...what about school?
I've got my military service, anyway.
So we'll reverse the gear.
We'll draw a letter R.
Do you know what R stands for?
Respect, I'll respect your decision.
It means whenever you want.
Whenever you are ready,
that's when we'll get married.
And when we shift to the fourth gear,
you'll drive the wedding car, okay?
Okay.
Come on in.
Welcome.
Let me kiss.
- Could you give us a second?
- Of course.
Well... take a seat, let me offer you tea.
No.
I was going to come
with my uncle actually.
No, don't come, son.
Don't come, don't bring your uncle.
Don't come to ask for
Belgin's hand in marriage.
If I say no to you now, I'll be at odds
with my daughter. Do you understand?
But we love each other so much.
Besides, I promised her.
I didn't go back to my hometown...
What promise, son?
You two are only kids.
Don't say that.
I'll dote upon her.
Don't worry.
Listen, Abdullah...
...do you think I wouldn't want to see my
daughter in a wedding dress?
But she has studies.
She has school.
She grew up like an orphan,
without a father.
She thinks her orphanhood will end
when she gets married.
It can't, it won't.
Son, she got into a very difficult school.
She won first place.
And you're in the way of her future.
Listen son, if you don't leave her,
my daughter won't leave you.
Think it through,
get out of her way.
That's all I have to say.
Oh, I love it too.
You've got carried away.
Stop playing with that cheap-jack ring.
Apparently, he upped and left.
That's not Abdullah.
You know that too.
If he wasn't caught up, if something bad
didn't happen to him, he would call.
We promised each other, Aysel.
Beautiful ma'am, take it.
It's beautiful.
- Take it, girl.
- No, thank...
Take it.
Flowers!
What's the state of this room?
It stinks here.
How do you live here?
Get up, get up!
My girl, come on.
I heated the water, take a bath.
I'll do the laundry, I'm waiting for you.
Come on, you've sank into the bed.
Leave me alone.
It annoys the hell out of me to
see you in this state.
My girl, I don't get it. You don't
go to school, you don't go to work.
What's this? You've let yourself go.
Do you know what ‘m going through?
What are you going through?
What is it?
Do you know how many people
would like to be in your place?
I don't want to know!
I don't want to know
how many people are unhappy like I am.
Whatever I touch, it breaks!
Look at me, stop talking madly
and don't drive me nuts.
- Let go of me!
- Off to the bathroom.
- Move, to the bathroom.
- Let go of me! I've had enough!
- She's gone mad...
- I've had enough... It hurts.
- Come on!
- I'm sick of you.
- Instead of crying for everything...
- Off you go!
- I'm sick of you and everyone.
Come on, finish school
as soon as possible.
I'm sick of it!
Enough!
Pass me a clothespin from there,
let your hand get used to being useful.
Belgin, I'm talking to you!
Give me a clothespin from here?
Good day to you, ma'am.
Do you have a minute?
I hope nothing's wrong.
Who are you looking for?
I'm here for your daughter.
Are you coming from the school?
Let me introduce myself.
I am Necati,
the director of the Feyman Club.
I've been trying to reach
Ms Belgin for days.
She caused quite a splash
when she sang in our club.
I wouldn't be surprised.
My daughter
is a schooled artist after all.
Let me put it to you this way.
Feyman is one of the most
decent places in Ankara.
Our business is frequented by
bureaucrats, businessmen and artists.
They don't only come to eat,
drink and have fun...
...they also come to listen to music.
Mr. İlhan, our boss,
gave me an instruction.
We'd be honoured to see a young talent
like Ms Belgin among us.
Unfortunately, my daughter has school.
It's pretty appropriate for me.
I am over 18.
You don't have to ask
my mother's permission.
Impossible.
I accept.
What about the post office?
I've just quit.
You need a stage name, then.
Bergen.
Is Bergen okay?
♪ Let me be the sob stuck in your throat ♪
♪ Don't forget me ♪
♪ I hope you won't be able to forget me ♪
♪ Let me be the tear
that cannot drop from your eye ♪
♪ Don't forget me ♪
♪ I hope you won't be able to forget me ♪
♪ Like your shadow, step by step ♪
♪ My name in every breath ♪
♪ Like I didn't forget you ♪
♪ Don't forget me, either ♪
♪ I hope you won't be able to forget me ♪
♪ Like your shadow, step by step ♪
♪ My name in every breath ♪
♪ Like I didn't forget you ♪
♪ Don't forget me, either ♪
♪ I hope you won't be able to forget me ♪
Yes, Ms.
Come, Belgin, come.
Ms, it happened by chance.
It's a really decent place.
Or else, you know,
my mother would never allow it.
Besides, I'm earning my pocket money
and supporting my mother.
I did my best but...
...it wasn't enough.
Belgin, this is a school.
It's a state institution.
Each student here...
...represents this institution, right?
We can't ignore it.
You performed on the stage knowing
it was forbidden.
It's very simple,
you'll either quit school or the stage.
Unfortunately, this is the case.
I wish I had a chance to choose, Ms.
My dad.
I have a few words for you, woman!
That's why I came here.
I wish you didn't bother
after all these years.
They told me Belgin became Bergen
and sang in night clubs.
I didn't believe it at first.
But it's true.
You humiliated me in Mersin!
- Dad, I...
- Dad?
You call him dad?
A dad? A feckless dad!
Do you have any idea?
That we warmed our bed
breathing into it at night.
We ate an egg in two days.
You weren't humiliated then
but you're humiliated now?
You shouldn't have left, then.
Who told you to go on your own
as a woman with a little kid?
Oh, how convenient!
You had a mistress within my earshot...
...and I was supposed to sit at home
and be quiet, eh?!
Do you think my honour was that cheap?
Damn your honour!
I'm taking the girl away with me.
And that's the end of it...
- It's over... This is over!
- Who are you taking?
I'm taking my daughter away with me.
Wait there!
"Taking my daughter".
You've changed so much.
You're taking your daughter, is that so?
She wrote you a letter every week.
Every week.
You didn't bother to read
even one of them!
Who is your daughter?
Is she your daughter? Eh?!
How come she is your daughter!
RETURNED
♪ I wonder if I could find ♪
♪ Find myself within me ♪
♪ The unlived years of my youth ♪
♪ And the reason for my silence ♪
♪ I wish I could meet myself there ♪
♪ And create with my own hands ♪
♪ A small castle of glass ♪
♪ With my friends, in my universe ♪
♪ It's not for nothing, I won't believe it ♪
♪ I'll be running after you again ♪
♪ Doesn't matter if I find or not ♪
♪ Know that It's the hope
that keeps me alive ♪
Ms Bergen,
we had a very good season thanks to you.
I hope to see you again next winter.
- Here it is.
- Thank you so much, thanks.
By the way,
I have a colleague who came from Adana.
He'd like to see you.
Of course.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Cevdet.
- Ms Bergen, hello.
- Hello.
This Necati, bless him, likes you so much.
He made me jump through hoops
to introduce me to Ms Bergen.
- Mr Minister is leaving, sir.
- Excuse me, excuse me.
Now, ma'am...
...I said it the first day
I listened to Ms Bergen.
I said this voice
would shake Adana to the ground.
I swear I was speechless.
Anyway, ma'am,
the purpose of my visit is...
...to make, by hook or crook...
...Ms Bergen perform on stage
in Adana this summer.
- Adana?
- Yeah.
Don't brush Adana off, ma'am.
The most respected singers of the country
perform in our place in Adana.
It's only for three months.
Your place here is reserved
for the winter, anyway.
No, my daughter doesn't
want to work in summer.
Still, I think you should give...
...it a thought and ask around.
Thank you.
With your permission.
So long, ma'am.
I'm closing the door.
Mom...
...the last dress you sewed...
...do you think I can wear it in Adana
if we go there?
What is it, babe?
Did your tassels fall down?
My goodness.
Oh, ma'am, welcome.
Welcome, We've been waiting for you
for a long time.
Go ahead, take a seat.
- You came from the road, are you hungry?
- No.
- What shall I order for you, kebab?
- No, we're full.
- Or let me order tea or a cold drink...
- No, thank you so much.
The driver's waiting; we'll go back
to the hotel. We wanted to say hi.
I'm glad you did.
Thank you for coming.
Well, Ms Bergen, you'll perform
in the classiest place in Adana.
Mr Cevdet, let me tell you from the start.
I'll sing my songs and leave.
I came here as a singing artist.
If things go different,
we'll go back to Ankara immediately.
God forbid.
Even the slightest thing
that would bother...
...or confuse you will
never happen here.
You are most welcome here.
- I have something to say too...
- Ma'am...
...you can come and leave here with
your daughter.
Like I said,
you are most welcome here.
Yes, our esteemed guests...
...please welcome the singer who...
...became famous in Adana...
...and conquered hearts with her voice...
...the most beautiful Bergen.
♪ I've got the suffering,
you've got the cure ♪
♪ I've got the love, you've got the decree ♪
♪ You've got the heart that kills me ♪
♪ Makes me smile and cry every day ♪
♪ Even though the seasons
may come and pass ♪
♪ Even though this love
makes me lose myself ♪
♪ Even though life on earth may end ♪
♪ Still, I've got the immortal love ♪
♪ I don't want separation
to make me destitute ♪
♪ I don't want it to taint my love ♪
♪ I only loved you even in my dreams ♪
♪ I don't want the leaves
to fall down in the fall ♪
♪ Your love is a blaze and
your longing is ember ♪
♪ Ask my heart about your absence ♪
♪ I feel like I came into the world
with you ♪
♪ It's hard to imagine living without you ♪
Thank God, tonight's over too.
You are the cruellest singer
I've ever seen.
You give blaze and create ember.
What on earth does that mean?
You put the horseshoe into the fire.
You have no mercy.
My girl,
we haven't been able to tell if you...
...insult or compliment
since the day we came here.
Oh, fine.
Bravo. Like it?
Alright.
Right, open it.
Who was that silly man who threw roses?
Oh, he's harmless.
Okkes, the owner of the liver place.
Don't worry. He can't come anymore
even if he wants to.
And what about that man
in the opposite box?
The tall one?
He only needs to raise an eyebrow.
Don't be surprised if he has
the Othello syndrome.
What's the Othello syndrome?
What did you blurt out again?
I mean he is obsessed.
Don't you know a foreign language?
Good God.
I've had enough of your...
Oh, don't even stoop to shoot the breeze.
Model citizens going from work to home.
Don't you have a life?!
I'll make tea now.
That would be great. I'm hungry.
We have something to eat, right?
Cookies etc...
Oh, God...
What a disgrace!
What kind of disgrace is this?!
Who entered our room?
I don't understand who allowed this!
How could this happen?
I can't believe someone freely...
...walked into the room just like that!
I'm asking you, bald head!
I'm asking you who allowed this?!
Gosh...
Is this a barn or a hotel?
Where are we staying?
There's something called privacy!
How could this happen?!
How could it happen?!
Here we go, enjoy your new car.
I made the first payment
with your down-payment.
You can pay the rest by instalments.
Get in, ma'am, come on, get in.
Girls, drop me home, will you!
Do me some good, eh?
Jump in, jump in!
It's beautiful,
the car's just like a girl.
Enjoy your new car, sis.
Maybe you can sew a lucky charm
for my new car.
- There's a telegram for you.
- Mom...
...wait.
"Our father is in hospital,
he's in a critical condition."
From my sister Hatice.
Dad...
It's me...
...Belgin.
Actually, we're very close.
We're in Adana.
I have a good job.
They love me there.
And I bought a car too.
It's red.
When you get better,
I can take you out for a ride.
Hope he recovers soon.
How dare you come here?
Is it the time for it now, brother-in-law?
I let her know; she deserves to be here.
Why did you ask her to come, Hatice?
Didn't your father say, "I don't care if
the singer and she who allowed this die"?
Why did you do this to a sick man?
What are you talking about?
He's her father too.
Let him! Let him vomit his hatred.
It's as if I entered
the enemy's territory.
There's no enmity, dear Belgin.
It's just that your life is
unfathomable for us, that's why.
His only wish was
for you to start a family.
He wanted you to have a normal life
like all of us.
Normal?
You all have a father!
All of you!
We are seven siblings, Nadire.
They all gathered for him...
...only I'm not wanted.
Just because I perform on stage.
He'll love me only if I get married.
I haven't been able to sleep for days.
It's the same nightmare
over and over again.
Girl, look at me...
...at least you have a father
who is upset with you.
Do you think he'd be upset with you
if he didn't have a dream for you?
Count your blessings.
What if your dad had a gambling debt?
What if you learned what a vile place
the world is from your dad?
It'll go straight to your head, girl.
Easy.
Look...
...a certain Don Puan bought
chocolate for you.
Eat it.
I hid it
so your mother wouldn't get angry.
Top it, will you?
So tell me what this nightmare's about
There is a giant tree...
...I guess it's near our house in Mersin.
And then, a white pigeon.
It turns around, flies...
...and tries to land on that tree.
But it can't.
And then, for hours...
...maybe for days...
...it flies... flies... flies.
And it gets tired in the end.
Boy, run!
Bring cologne and water!
I've become a burden to you.
Don't mention it.
If I wasn't by your side...
...I'd be worried sick.
- Let me give this...
- No... You are very cold.
Keep it.
My mother must be worried.
I should go now.
We will.
Thank you.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Well, I've composed myself.
You were very cold...
...and there was nothing else we could do.
What is it? Did you see someone you know?
Myself.
My mouth, my face looks
all over the place. And you don't tell me.
Oh, don't, be fair with yourself.
When I look at you...
...I see a shy gazelle.
An elegant...
...gazelle among the red roses.
Why didn't you go to bed?
Where were you, my girl?
I was scared to death.
They said you fainted.
Don't worry, I'm okay.
Wait, let's take these off.
The car was broken,
we went to the soup place.
Is this why you're late?
- Oh, God...
- I'll tell you in the morning.
Let's take these off.
Let's take your clothes off.
No, I don't want to.
Sleep. We'll talk later.
- Oh, no, you can't go to bed like this.
- I'll sleep like this.
Hasan, bring the car, will you?
Let's go to my place, girl.
I'll make you coffee.
And read your fortune.
Really?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Hasan.
- Yes, ma'am.
- The car?
- The car's not here, ma'am.
- What do you mean?
It's not here.
Boy, did she come with a coach?
Where is the car?
I have the key but the car isn't here.
Zeynel, did you take the car for a wash?
No, ma'am, I didn't.
How?!
I parked it here.
Hasn't anyone seen it?
What's going on? What happened?
What was the model?
What colour was the car?
It's a bloody red car, brother.
Oh, how many times has it been?!
They must have taken and broken it
into pieces already. Scoundrels!
Oh, don't jinx it.
We'll take care of, Ms Bergen.
Don't worry, we'll take care of it.
Thank you.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
How can a car be stolen in the middle
of the day in broad daylight?
And it has a lot of debt too.
We'll go back to Ankara
at the end of the season.
Don't worry.
Don't be worrying yourself.
There you go.
Did you pay for all of it?
Thank you so much
but I can't accept this.
This is my debt.
Keep the bills, I'll pay all of it.
A shame, really.
I mean...
Am I inglorious enough to keep the woman
I love in debt?
Oh, that's so lovely of you but
I didn't mean to say that.
Lovely, sure.
Can't do without love.
So you'll make me perish
on the road to Ankara.
Maybe you'll think, "oh, poor thing"...
And won't go to Ankara.
Just ask, and I'll...
...I'll be your everything.
Let God be my witness.
One can't get enough of looking at you...
...or listening to you.
Oh, stop moving.
Or I'll prick it somewhere.
Sister Sabahat, you've covered me.
Where will I go in this?
To a housewives meeting?
Put some décor in.
This is the first time I'm sewing
a belly-dancer thing in my life.
What's a décor, my girl?
I mean, open it.
I'll get hot in this.
Oh, God, let us return to Ankara and...
Here, I opened it.
If I even mention these days,
I'll change my name.
Why?
Bergen loves it here.
Yes, a lot.
Belgin's head is in the clouds.
Where has she been going for weeks?
She says she goes shopping.
Or to the hair dresser's.
I hope we pay this bill and
get rid of this place.
The car's debt is cleared.
What are you talking about, my girl?
It's not that easy.
It turns out Don Puan's shit is big.
That tall man, remember?
What on earth
are you talking about, Nadire?
I'm saying it turns out
he's a generous man.
He paid all the bills...
...went before Bergen and
tore them apart.
Could you take these in?
I came to say goodbye.
Are you leaving?
Depends on you.
If you say stay, I'll stay.
My car!
You've found it before
it was broken into pieces.
Well...
I know how to look out for what I own.
I made a couple of phone calls,
and friends from the police station
helped too.
Thanks to them,
we've found it easily.
You really said you'd take care of it.
Whatever you heard about me is true,
Ms Bergen, you'll get used to it.
I've already gotten used to you.
If you like you can go...
...or stay and...
...be my wife.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy right now.
There is one thing
I want from you, though.
If you marry me...
...singing in night clubs is beneath us.
How?
But I don't want to quit music.
I'm not asking you to quit music, doll.
We'll make you a record
from good companies.
And organize public concerts.
Adana is nothing.
We'll make you the star of Turkey.
It's beautiful to even dream about.
I'll go insane.
What do you mean you're getting married?
Have you gone mad?
That man is old enough to be your father.
Did he put you in a situation
where you have to?
Mom, don't be ridiculous.
What are you talking about?
This man loves me madly.
He wouldn't harm a hair on my head.
I don't trust this man at all.
Who is he? What is he about?
What does he do? We know nothing.
And you've already said yes
without taking my blessing.
You have, haven't you?
I'm just a scarecrow here, right?
Oh, it's about Ms Sabahat again.
No, it's about you.
Shouldn't I have a family too?
Is that so? A family?
Then, why did you write off the name
I gave you in a second?
Go ahead, write me off too.
What does it have to do with that?
I don't see the relevance.
I'm just quitting the stage.
Why, then, have we been stuck
in these hotel rooms?
Why did we leave our home, my girl?
Weren't you saying, "I'm an artist...
...the stage is my home,
love, my passion."?
What happened? Why are you quitting now?
I'm not quitting music,
I just won't perform on stage
He said we'd release records
and organize public concerts instead.
"We?"
Who is he?!
Who is he to have a say about your future?
Will it be you?
Do you want me to end up like you?
What's wrong with how I ended up?
Lonesome, full of resentment and anger.
I'll never be like you, mom, never!
I see.
So you want me to hand
my daughter over to this..
...shady man with my own hands,
is that so?
Yes, that's what I want.
Over my dead body!
Yes.
Dad...
How are you?
You look better.
Oh, no, don't get up.
Look who I've taken here for you.
Let me introduce you, your son-in-law.
We got married today.
My girl, congratulations.
If I had known...
Oh, no, thanks.
I didn't want to tire you out
because you are sick.
Besides, we only had a simple ceremony.
Let me go get tea.
And you can have a chat in the meantime.
It's good that
you are transferred to a private room.
Do you have kids?
You say it's early now but...
...why should we wait?
Let us not wait.
Let's have a child.
Or is it that you don't love me?
There's no such thing, my gazelle-eyed.
Do you think I'd be after you
if I didn't love you?
But wait, let's take our time.
Don't rush.
Everything's still so new.
Oh, come on.
Our house will become so cheerful
when the baby comes.
And my mom will forgive me.
She can't resist it,
she'll come right away.
I don't understand why your mother
didn't come to the wedding, anyway.
What was her issue?
She would have come but...
...I said some hard things.
Don't wait for me for dinner.
I'll eat out with the governor.
Cevdet brought
such a beautiful woman to the club.
I swear...
...her voice is as beautiful as
she is herself.
I'm sure they'll make her a record.
Did Nadire like her too?
How many times do I have to tell you,
my gazelle-eyed?
A married woman should have
nothing to do with a belly dancer.
Do you cook every day?
Bending over backwards for him and all.
Don't you go out?
He comes home tired from work at night.
When can we go out?
I saw him in the bank the other day.
He had this air on.
I called out to him but he didn't care.
He must have not heard you.
He works, gets tired.
So... Do they ask about me in the club?
Well, you absence is felt, of course.
Don't you miss it?
What difference would it make
if I did for God's sake?
Turns out they are a false friend, anyway.
I heard there's this new girl
and she sounds like heaven.
Oh, she thinks she's so cool.
You'd think she is beautiful
from a distance.
Up close, that's not the case at all.
People keep asking about you.
Nothing gets full circle, Nadire.
I went to school, there was no school.
I performed on the stage,
I didn't have my dad.
I got married, there is no stage.
When one thing comes full circle,
the other one breaks.
You are not the kind of woman
to sit at home all day.
Or your ass will get bigger.
Come from time to time
and get the dust off the stage.
You said you wouldn't be late
and now it's morning.
What's that suit?
What are you talking about?
You had the white one on last night?
What's this?
You've lost your mind.
I've come in the suit I left.
Gosh.
- Hello.
I haven't been able to say
"welcome" for a while.
I wonder if you are available now.
Who is it?
Our neighbour, love.
What on earth are you doing?
Slamming the door on her, it's rude...
I long for the face of a human being.
I miss my mom.
You miss your mom
who didn't even come to your wedding, eh?
You'd think
I took her daughter away to a mountain.
I long for the people I love.
Is this marriage?
Yes, I miss my mom.
Your mom sold you to the night club.
Who saved you?
Me.
What are you talking about?
It was a decent night club!
Remember,
I quit the stage because you asked me to.
Not because
I was ashamed of working there.
You were a side dish
for all the drunken men there!
And you were there every night.
Was I your side dish too?
They made you dependent on them
through the bills.
Wake up to these.
Who paid for it? Me?
I was paying it just fine. I wasn't
in need of you. I didn't need you.
Who took the car from the thieves?
- Me.
- So...?
You got it and what did you do with it?
You sold it as soon as you got it back.
I would have left Adana
if I had wanted to.
Didn't you beg me not to leave?
Didn't you say, "I'm so in love with you"?
I'm not your concubine.
I don't know what your problem is
but it is something you need to sort
from within.
I've got a mom, a dad and a family.
I love you so much that...
I swear to God
I always see you wherever I look.
Come on, let's forget everything.
Let's pretend it never happened.
You and I will be so happy.
We'll have children.
And I'll...
...I'll make you the happiest woman
in Adana.
Let's forget.
Hello?
Mom.
Belgin.
My lamb.
How are you?
I'm very good.
Thank God, there's nothing wrong. You?
Good, good.
Mualla's daughter's getting married
this evening and we're rushing about.
You are left on your own.
Oh, no, my child.
The neighbours etc.,
they all take good care of me, bless them.
Only at night...
And you aren't here then
so I feel at ease.
Are you okay?
Is everything alright?
We...
We were in Uludag,
we've just come back.
In fact, I was buried in snow
up to my waist...
...my husband took me back
to the hotel in a sled.
Good, I just want you to be happy.
Mom, I'm sorry about those things I said.
Never mind, I've already forgotten.
Mothers don't remain
resentful of their children.
You'll understand soon.
I'll call you again
at the first opportunity.
In fact, maybe I'll come.
I wish you did.
Come on, get up and set the table.
I've got things to tell you.
Let me wash up first.
What do you do? I don't get it.
What do I say if someone asks me?
Do I say you're a car dealer?
Or are you a broker?
A real estate agent?
You've had too much to drink
you're talking nonsense. Watch it.
You're absent for weeks.
I don't know where you spend the night.
You keep changing cars.
You leave in one suit
and come in another one.
I see.
Clothing business.
What do you want?
Look...
...I got you a house in the best
neighbourhood. What more do you want?
Yes, there's a house, it's impressive..
But there's no home.
There's nothing but four walls.
I have neither a husband...
...nor a friend.
I miss my mom.
Tomorrow...
...I'm going back to Ankara.
Did you hear me?
And that's that.
Don't! Don't!
Belgin?
Belgin, my girl.
Oh, wow, Ms Sabahat.
I've been on the lookout for you.
Where have you been?
God, give me patience.
Stop talking nonsense.
You, saucy.
Oh, you've got a big mouth.
How did you find me?
It's no secret
where the likes of you fool around.
Take me to my daughter immediately.
And she gives me instruction.
So brave of you.
Why should it take bravery
to ask about my daughter?
What did you do to her?
Where is Belgin?
What do you think?
I married her,
and now she sits at home sheepishly.
No.
I've asked around,
no one has ever seen her face.
Where is this girl?
Look here, don't get on my nerves.
She's at home.
What home?
I am her home. Do you get it?
Do you think Belgin has no one?
Your daughter quit the world for me.
Who are you?
Remember what you've just said
when she leaves.
How is that going to happen?
Quite easily.
Because she'll come back
once she understands what you're about.
You...
...you stole a girl's youth.
Listen...
...I know what I'd do to you
if you were a man but...
Anyway... Fuck off now!
Mind your manners, look at me!
My name is Sabahat.
Did you hear me?
If you hurt a hair on her head...
...I swear I'll beat the hell out of you.
Sabahat, do you know what fear is?
You had better be afraid.
I learned what it is
from scoundrels like you.
An hour, Sabahat.
If you don't leave Adana within an hour,
I'll take it out on your daughter.
Godless scoundrel!
Thank you.
This way.
- See you later.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
You can't make it up to me
with a necklace.
No.
I can't.
But I may ease it.
Oh, come on. Come on.
Don't do this.
Come on.
Don't look at me like that.
Okay, I couldn't hold myself back.
I lost my cool.
I just snapped.
But I'm a human being, right?
It caught me off guard.
If I raise my hand...
...to hit you again, I'm a scoundrel.
Promise?
I swear.
What shall we do tonight?
Shall I take you out?
- You'll loosen up and have some fun.
- My mom came here today.
What?
My mom came.
I couldn't open the door for her.
I couldn't.
What goes around comes around,
brother Cevdet.
Watch your tongue, Nadire.
You besieged Bergen and set her up.
What are you talking about?
There's no such thing.
Don't get on my nerves in public.
Don't spin me a tale.
You put together a narrative
and got her into trouble.
There's no such thing. Stay out of it,
mind your own business, Nadire.
And you dragged me into it too...
...may God damn you.
May whoever caused this
become a log in hell.
Well...
I'm so sorry, excuse me.
Could you sing along too, please?
Please.
Yes, friends,
our beloved Bergen is here among us.
An applause for Bergen.
G sharp minor.
Of course.
♪ Was it only you who cried? ♪
♪ Was it only you who got burned? ♪
♪ I couldn't smile, either ♪
♪ In the fake world ♪
♪ Did you think I was happy from within? ♪
♪ In this world that stole
my life for nothing ♪
♪ Oh, this fake world, in this fake world ♪
♪ In this world that gave me a fake smile ♪
♪ Oh, in this fake world,
in this fake world ♪
♪ In this world that gave me a fake smile ♪
Bergen?
Here, sis, drink
Have a couple of sips, come on.
Scoundrel!
And the half-wit liar beat you on top of
the other shit he put you through.
Liar?
I heard he is married.
And he has two grown-up sons.
He organized a fake wedding for you.
Even the devil can't think of
such a thing. They pulled one over on us.
Us?
I've...
...been locked in that house for months.
I've been tortured.
Did you know this?
I learned only today at the bank.
I ran to you right away
but you weren't there, sis.
I feel like dirt.
How did I fall into this trap?
Come, sis...
...let's go somewhere no one can find us.
We'll go where the cursed...
...belles, waning head turners are.
Where sugarplum ladies are.
Where the have-nots...
...and the poor queens gather.
Go over there.
Come, my girl.
Come.
Come here.
Come, dear, come.
♪ For a lover ♪
♪ I left you ♪
♪ Ask my conscience ♪
♪ How much I suffered ♪
♪ I leave myself ♪
♪ In your care ♪
♪ Strangers don't know ♪
♪ My worth at all, mom ♪
♪ No one loves me know ♪
♪ As much as you do, mom ♪
♪ If you run into your baby
with tears in her eyes ♪
♪ Forgive her mistake ♪
♪ And give her a hug ♪
♪ While we had our own life ♪
♪ We were deceived ♪
♪ Strangers don't know my worth at all,
mom ♪
♪ No one loves me ♪
♪ As much as you do, mom! ♪
♪ You devastated me ♪
♪ Ruined me at my young age ♪
♪ I'll haunt you even on the Judgment Day ♪
♪ You promised me a lot ♪
♪ I lost everything I had ♪
♪ I got a bad reputation ♪
♪ Be ashamed of what you did ♪
♪ Why did I meet you ♪
♪ How could I believe you ♪
I'm sorry for our loss.
♪ I'll haunt you ♪
Oh, fake world
♪ Even on the Judgment Day ♪
♪ I'll haunt you even on the Judgment Day ♪
♪ You promised me a lot ♪
♪ I lost everything I had ♪
♪ I got a bad reputation ♪
♪ Be ashamed of what you did ♪
My dear dad...
My dear...
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Belgin, don't!
- My condolences.
- How dare you come here!
One would be ashamed to!
How can I leave you alone
on a funeral day?
No way.
Alright, you offered your condolence,
go now.
- Wait.
- Let go of me.
The deceased
would want it to be this way too.
Keep my dad out of it.
He would.
He would like you to have
someone to look out for you.
I was going to ask
the deceased's blessing, anyway.
I was but, you never know what's next.
Bergen, listen to me.
Hear me out.
And then, you can do whatever you want.
But hear me out first.
Alright...
...I don't mind if I do.
Let me hear another bag of lies.
What would I lose?
He drove you
out of your wits just like that.
He said he had things to say.
As if I don't.
If you go there,
I swear I won't speak with you.
Oh, no, no chance.
Supposedly, my dad left me in his care.
He was going to ask for my dad's blessing.
As if...
He was fighting for his life, it wasn't
like he would think of you, then.
Why not, sister?
Maybe he was worried about me?
How about that?
I'm her youngest daughter.
Belgin.
Welcome.
Finally, at last.
Bekir and Ms Serap is his wife.
Hello.
And this is my famous Bergen.
- Welcome, take a seat.
- Welcome.
- Come, sit.
- Sit.
- Hello.
- Hello, welcome.
No, I won't drink.
I'll get on the road
early tomorrow morning.
Oh, no!
You like Raki.
Do you think I'm here to have fun!
Oh, I swear...
...I love this girl so much that...
...it drives me crazy.
I'm going to lose my mind, go nuts.
And I was married back then.
And Bergen was a well-bred girl.
She goes everywhere with her mother.
What could I have done?
So I lied.
And then... lies after lies.
I made a mess of it, of course.
Seems a shame,
you, poor things,
Poor us.
I took out all...
...my anger out of this sinless girl
who did nothing wrong.
Anyway, it's over now.
It's not. No, wait.
No way.
How can it be over?
I tried so much to forget about you.
So much.
But it didn't work.
I can't do without you.
Adana doesn't feel the way it did before.
Everything seems empty without you.
Let's not bore your friends
with our history.
Look, see?
Heard what she said?
My darling.
We do have a history.
Of course.
- Come on.
Excuse me, have fun.
Bergen, wait a second, wait.
What are you doing?
Are you staging a play here
with your friends?
What are you talking about?
Bekir is an old friend.
How the hell can I trust you now?
Bergen.
I regret it bitterly!
I caused this darkness
and I'll bring the light.
Come on, don't be stubborn.
Let's have our wedding for all to see.
Let everyone see...
...who I am and what our love is.
I can't believe it!
How could you allow your sister to go?
Oh, no... What were you thinking?
Mommy,
I thought she'd talk to him and be back.
How could I have known this would happen?
Who knows where she is?
Mersin is a big city.
How will we find her?
What's this?
Is this a joke?
Take it off now!
Did he put you in a wedding dress?
Mom...
...we got married.
I won't give you to that man,
do you understand?
- Mom!
- Mom, stop!
I can protect myself.
How can you?
Were you able to do it before?
For God's sake...
For God's sake, say something.
Your youth is gone.
Because of that ill-omened scoundrel.
Your youth is wasted!
I'm begging you...
For God's sake, please say something.
- Mommy... Calm down...
- I'm begging you, say something.
Okay, calm down.
Don't do this, Belgin, I'm begging you.
Alright... My gazelle-eyed.
Pour the Raki.
Well...
...my period is two weeks late.
But it happens.
Oh, God willing.
God willing.
I hope
we have a gazelle-eyed daughter like you.
I swear I'll sacrifice forty rams.
You are not to drink Raki
until we know for sure, though.
Cheers.
Wait, wait.
Fuck off!
Go and play somewhere else!
You, brats!
Did your father ever beat you up?
Oh, God.
Every father beats up their child,
my gazelle-eyed.
My father never beat me up.
Your father deserted you
like a puppy, girl.
You don' know
what a father is supposed to be like.
A father should be strong.
My father was.
He would beat us up when we deserved it.
And he would also care for us.
And you'll both beat up and
care for your child, is that so?
Fuck that kind of love!
Fuck off!
♪ I have a complaint about fate ♪
I'll get off when we turn the corner.
I don't have cash on me.
Take this, brother.
Oh, no way.
Keep it.
You can cash it.
I won't wear it anymore.
Girl, there are so many eggplants.
What's up?
Are you starting a trading business?
This is barely enough for five families.
We could even do more.
Mukadder doesn't even
think of eating something else.
Besides, what did you use to eat in Ankara
all winter, my ungrateful child?
Thank you.
It's good, isn't it?
Mukadder brought it from Germany.
Garlic crusher, grater.
Skirt, shoes and the fancy stuff
are for you.
See how elegant this is.
Her eyes land upon
the beautiful all the time.
You've always admired Mukadder.
Why did you say that? I admire you too.
What could you admire about me
for God's sake?
Of course, I do.
I admire everything about you.
Bergen!
Open the door, Bergen!
Open!
Bergen!
What's going on? Belgin isn't here!
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
I went home and the woman wasn't there!
Bergen!
Where are you? Come out!
Where the hell are you?
She is my wife!
Even if she goes to her grave, I'll take
her bones, counting them one by one.
You will all pay for this!!
All of you!
My house is on fire!
God, save us.
♪ From those who disregard love ♪
♪ And those who devastate through longing ♪
♪ From the merciless ♪
Mom, we're going. Now.
♪ Save me, God,
Save me, God ♪
♪ Save me, God
♪ From the merciless ♪
♪ I've had enough, God ♪
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL BERGEN
♪ Save me, God ♪
♪ From these traps I fall into ♪
Mom!
Help!
ACID THROWN IN BERGEN'S FACE
42 HOURS LATER
THE JEALOUS HUSBAND THROWS ACID
THESE EYES CANNOT SEE
There's severe necrosis
on the surface of the skin.
The surgical interventions
were performed as much as possible.
We may be able to save one of her eyes.
Please, let her live,
I'll look after of her.
We'll do all we can.
I'll look after her...
Mom, can you give me water?
Okay, my girl.
Hello.
God damn you!
How dare you call this place?
You, heathen...
You, prick!
You made me fucking blind!
What are you still talking about?
What a baseborn, inglorious,
vile, miserable man you are!
I swear I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Listen...
...the police are after me.
They're looking for me everywhere.
Withdraw your complaint.
Withdraw your complaint...
...or I'll bring that hospital down
around you.
I swear to God I didn't do it.
It wasn't me!
Listen to me, listen to me carefully.
If you don't withdraw your complaint...
...I'll rip off your mom's liver.
Did you hear me?
I'll rip it off.
All you can do is unleash your vile men
on me, you, heathen!
Don't you believe in God?
How could you do this to me?
How could one do this to someone he loves?
Even the soil
won't accept your love anymore.
May you not live a day of
peace and draw...
...a sigh of relief till you die!
Never!
I'm sorry to hear what happened.
I've come to see Belgin, ma'am.
No, mom.
Send him away.
If you need anything,
please don't hesitate to give me a call.
It would be better
if she had some time alone.
By the way, we've discharged her.
You can go home whenever you want.
She'll undergo two more operations.
Her entire treatment should end
within two years.
2 YEARS LATER
The past is in the past.
Stop disagreeing.
Why, though, I've had enough.
Let me drink this demon drink and leave.
I'm telling you I want you to perform
at the New York Club,
why don't you believe me?
Why, bro?
So that people feel sorry for me?
You'll turn me into a circus freak.
It's not about feeling sorry.
We were upset. Yes.
But it's enough.
Look, you can't waste this voice.
Besides, do you think I'd take this risk
if I didn't believe in you?
Come with me, come.
Bergen...
...what you're going through isn't easy.
I can't even imagine the pain you suffer.
But you still have your voice.
And it'll be a shame if you stop singing.
This is Bergen, the woman who had
acid thrown in her face, you know.
Look who's here.
- Isn't she Bergen?
- She is.
- She's covered her eye with a tape, see?
- Yes.
- Does she play the cello?
- I don't know.
It made me so upset.
I had no idea.
Here it is, Ms Bergen.
Here comes the moment
you've all been looking forward to.
Our esteemed guests...
...after the disaster that befell her,
she is on stage for the first time here.
A very powerful voice,
a very powerful performance.
A round of applause for Bergen.
♪ I chased you out of my heart ♪
♪ You can't get back in ♪
♪ I cursed you ♪
♪ You can't come back ♪
♪ I chased you out of my heart ♪
♪ You can't get back in ♪
♪ I cursed you ♪
♪ You can't come back ♪
♪ You can't love anyone ♪
♪ You don't deserve happiness ♪
♪ You are not to be loved and smile ♪
♪ Your regret means nothing ♪
♪ You can't come back ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ You can't smile ♪
♪ Means nothing ♪
♪ You can't love ♪
♪ I gave you love
What did you do with it? ♪
♪ You threw it on the floor ♪
♪ You ruined us both ♪
♪ You can't wipe away the past ♪
♪ I gave you love
What did you do with it? ♪
♪ You threw it on the floor ♪
♪ You ruined us both ♪
♪ You can't wipe away the past ♪
BERGEN IS BREAKING RECORDS
♪ You don't deserve happiness ♪
♪ You can't be loved and smile ♪
♪ Your regret means nothing ♪
♪ You can't come back ♪
What is it?
Do you like your work of art?
I don't understand why you complain.
Thanks to me,
the entire Turkey knows you now.
I brought the stuff you asked for,
take them later.
Thanks, you took the trouble.
Yes, that's what my mother says too.
I was going to kill
that mother of yours but.
Your issue is with me.
Stay away from my family.
Forget my mother's name.
Do you understand?
Forget my mother's name!
Whore.
I would take offense in the past but...
...now, it's not working at all.
I'm dead certain there's no whore
out there that's vile like you are.
Ms Bergen...
Can we take a photo?
How did it go?
May I present to you...
...the female arabesque singer of the year
who sold over a million
cassette tapes with...
...her album "The Woman of Agonies"...
...and is awarded the Golden Record...
...Bergen.
Thanks to you, Bergen will no longer be
the woman of agonies.
Listen to my music
but don't feel sad for me.
I wouldn't be here were it not for you.
Thank you so much.
Help! Call the ambulance!
Quick, the ambulance...
Call the ambulance!
If I was afraid of death...
...I wouldn't be Bergen.
♪ Your eyes are wet ♪
♪ Never bow your head ♪
♪ Separation is not a matter of honour ♪
♪ Don't feel sad for me ♪
♪ From now on,
I'll mention your name once in a blue moon ♪
♪ I'll look for what I lost in you
in someone else ♪
♪ From now on,
I'll mention your name once in a blue moon ♪
♪ I'll look for what I lost in you
in someone else ♪
♪ Don't feel sad for me ♪
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
Just a second.
What's this, sis?
When did this man get out of prison
and approach you?
And you grinned.
You believed that too, Nadire?
I saw it with my own eyes,
of course, I do.
I'm sorry but
it turns out you're sort of crazy too.
- You look good together.
- Don't say that.
He said it was a matter of
reputation for him...
...and asked me to pose for the camera
just for show now that
I wasn't going back with him.
And I agreed
just so I could get rid of him.
Unbelievable.
Jerk.
Don't look at me, I'm ashamed.
I've been ashamed for years.
And yet, I've done nothing
to be ashamed of.
But I got a beating...
...and I wanted to hide my face in shame.
They made me blind, I was ashamed.
I couldn't open the door to my mom...
...I was ashamed.
I haven't felt ashamed only while singing.
Well, I don't feel ashamed only
while doing the belly dance.
Sis, your suffering
has been quite fancy, though.
I swear it's been earth-shaking.
Well done, girl.
Fancy or not,
it's still suffering, Nadire.
Whoever I leaned on for all these years,
they came crashing down.
I don't want to suffer anymore.
But you know, I...
...no matter what happens...
...want to continue to believe in roses.
There hasn't even been a day
I didn't think about you, Belgin.
Shall I believe it?
You said It's easy to put a ring on,
what's hard is to carry it.
I couldn't carry it.
And the ring I wore after yours...
...ruined me.
- Aren't you afraid?
- Very much so.
In fact, I'm exhausted with fear.
What can I do?
Not sing?
As if I don't exist.
Will you be able to forgive me?
That's the easiest part.
If I can manage to love without bruises...
...that's when I'll forgive myself.
This is good; it's elastic.
It's just come out, right?
I'll make a tight top with this...
...and a long tailed bottom.
A thick belt here.
You'll look like a doll but...
...do you have colours that
are more solid?
Plain colours.
I wonder what my life would be like
if I married a footballer.
Green, dark green, almond green.
I don't know I'd be over the moon I guess.
If Abdullah had been my husband...
...I wouldn't have had to suffer so much
to protect you.
No mother
would want her child to suffer like this.
You had school, my girl.
I thought
I did the best thing for you at the time.
Do you like this?
Look here.
Can you cut two meters of this?
We'll be there in 20 minutes, brother.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you kidding me?
I thought you'd love it, brother.
Why the hell would I!
How can you love a whore?
She came and begged me.
I said no.
No chance.
You are a singer...
...no way.
And do you know what she did then?
The black gazelle stared into my eyes
and said...
..."I won't even sing".
"Take me and make me your wife...
...and I'll be your slave".
I didn't want it, of course.
I didn't want to be blind.
I said, "You are used to the chin-wag of
the night club,
you'll get me in trouble...
...I won't marry you."
Why are you looking at me like that?
Brother, you got a divorce...
That happened later.
I didn't marry her at first.
Then, I felt sorry for her.
I rented a house for her
and furnished it.
I told her to live there.
And when she thought the money
wasn't enough, she fucked off.
And then, her dad died.
Well, I'm a human being too, you know.
I went to offer my condolence.
And she was all over me there.
She kept insisting I marry her.
I was drunk, of course,
I had a bit too much to drink.
She played for sympathy.
And she said she became an orphan.
And she made me marry her.
Why are you gawking at me?
You, prick!
I fell into that whore's trap
because of mercy.
She didn't let go of me.
I went to prison
and she kept coming to visit and...
...crying and saying
"I can't be without you" etc.
She talked my head off.
That's what she did.
She did you many wrongs, brother.
She could have at least
corrected them, right?
We're all human after all.
I have a name, a reputation, right?
One puts up with it when in love,
of course.
Oh, I didn't love her!
It's all because of that snake, her mom.
She brainwashed her.
I should have crushed that snake
in the beginning but...
And I had the chance.
But I couldn't do it.
Kismet, you know.
Never mind, brother,
you are a merciful man.
And that's what suits you.
So what's up with you?
Did you ask for the girl's
hand in marriage?
Oh, no,
her dad doesn't give me the green light.
He said he wouldn't marry his daughter
off to a scum.
Elope with her, then.
She doesn't want that.
She says, she can't start a family
without her parents.
You let her take the reins.
Let me tell you one thing.
You take the girl, shut her in a house.
You feed her, take care of her.
You look after her until her time is up.
Women, you know.
They're like gazelles, of course.
Gazelles but...
...in a way, they're also a prey.
You shouldn't stare
into the eyes of your prey, though.
Or they'll take you in. And destroy you.
Next thing you know,
you are all over the place.
What happened?
Nothing.
Come.
Bergen!
Come here, come!
Come here!
I have a couple of things to say.
Come here.
Please, don't go.
Wait here.
Do you think he's her troubled ex?
What the hell did you do to me?
What did you do to me?
You ruined my reputation.
Look at me now.
What did you do to me?
You know I...
...I can't live without you, Bergen.
Oh, you can.
Don't worry, everyone can.
You are famous now, eh?
You are famous now, of course.
Famous.
What the hell are you talking about?
I only did the job I love doing.
Fuck your job!
Is this the job you love?
Come on, let's go back to our house.
What house are you talking about?
What house?!
To the dungeon?
What did you give to me other than pain?
You couldn't wait.
You just couldn't stop it.
You have to entertain drunken people, eh?
You know what, though...
...ingratitude runs through your blood.
You kept going on about your mom.
And everything happened
because of that mom of yours.
You tested me through my mom,
and her through me without shame.
Look at me.
Where the fuck is your dignity?
Tell me.
Look into my eyes.
I've been through hell because of you.
And now, I don't even hate you.
What's done is done.
We are done.
İbrahim, come, take him
and get the fuck out of here now.
And don't let me see you ever again.
My sister and I can pick stonecrop.
That would be so nice.
And we can make a stonecrop jam.
- The door, lock it!
- Bergen!
Open the door, open!
What do you want?
Aren't we done?
I still have things to say, Bergen.
- Please, don't leave the car.
- He can't harm me.
What? What do you want?
Bro, it's rude to cut off and all.
- Stop talking, she's my wife!
- What are you talking about?!
I'm not your wife or anything.
We are divorced, don't you understand?
You can't divorce me.
- Come on, we're going home.
- Let go of me!
To hell with your manhood!
No one needs such manhood.
You wasted my life!
I've had enough, go. Enough.
Mom!
♪ Oh, God, you may forgive
your evil subjects but I won't ♪
♪ You may forgive all the
cruel ones but I won't ♪
♪ You are God, you are forgiving
You may forgive your subjects ♪
♪ You know how much I suffered
You may forgive them but I won't ♪
♪ You may forgive them but I won't ♪
♪ You may forgive all the
cruel ones but I won't ♪
♪ Those who make you cry and laugh at you
Those who leave you and go ♪
♪ Those who are loved but don't love
You may forgive them but I won't ♪
Sabahat Sarilmiser, who was seriously
injured in the attack...
...was unaware of her daughter's death
while in the hospital.
Bergen was buried with a quiet ceremony
only her family could attend.
The grieving mother spent the rest of her
life with her daughter's photos...
...behind locked doors.
She lies next to her daughter
in the cage she had...
...constructed to protect
her daughter's bones.
The perpetrator fled to Germany
after the murder.
Following his extradition to Turkey,
he was sentenced to 15 years.
His sentence was reduced to
3 years due to good conduct.
Considering the period of imprisonment
in Germany and Turkey...
...he spent 7 months in prison.
The name of the perpetrator
is Halis Serbest!
Femicides began to be recorded in 1995..
4.289 WOMEN between 2002 and 2010!
Since 2011, when the Istanbul Convention
was signed;
Between 2011 and 2020, 2.490 women
were killed and taken from us...